{
  "shortDescription": "Test your knowledge of TOKEN $DEGEN.",
  "questions": [
    {
      "question": "What is $DEGEN?",
      "answers": ["Token", "Game", "Book"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "Who created $DEGEN?",
      "answers": ["Community", "Bank", "Corp"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "What is $DEGEN used for?",
      "answers": ["Trading", "Gaming", "Shopping"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "What blockchain is $DEGEN on?",
      "answers": ["BASE", "Bitcoin", "Solana"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "What does 'DEGEN' stand for?",
      "answers": ["Degenerate", "Design", "Development"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "What is staking?",
      "answers": ["Holding", "Selling", "Mining"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "What is a DApp?",
      "answers": ["App", "Coin", "Token"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "What is a DAO?",
      "answers": ["Org", "Coin", "Game"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "What is DeFi?",
      "answers": ["Finance", "Gaming", "Tech"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "Where can you trade $DEGEN?",
      "answers": ["DEX", "Bank", "Store"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "Have you followed @watchcoin?",
      "answers": ["Yes", "No", "Soon"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 2
    }
  ]
}
